U-chan, you're so cute.
Woo-chan!
Hello! I'm Mr. Nokotte Kurumi no crab, U-chan!
Today, I'd like to introduce a new project! Today I'd like to introduce a new project!
I'd like to go on a tour with my Boston Terrier, Woo-chan, who is the staff's favorite dog.
We're going to visit various places where you can have fun with your pooch!
Ushimi-chan, nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you today, so it's a little bit difficult for me to get to know U-chan, but I hope we can get to know each other.
In order to get along with Ucchan, I'd like to do many things that I think will make her happy.
I'm looking forward to working with you, Ucchan.
Ucchan is so energetic!
Ucchan is suddenly very energetic!
Where are you going, Ucchan?
Let's go this way, U-chan.
U-chan, let's go this way.
U-chan, you're so energetic!
Amazing!
So energetic!
Let's walk a little slower.
I'm so happy.
He ran a lot.
U-chan, stairs!
A little bit slower, okay?
I don't want you to slip a little.
Your back is so cute!
Look, Woo-chan, there's a hydrangea.
There's a hydrangea.
So beautiful!
I've run a lot, so I'd like to take a break with Woo-chan.
I'm Woo-chan, Woo-chan's color
I had an espresso ahogado Frappuccino!
Let's refuel soon, Woo-chan!
Actually, Woo-chan, earlier, I thought you'd be happy with
Pawpaw bread!
I got the pawpaw madeleines!
Want some? Let's eat it together.
If I say eat it with you, I'll eat it with you.
I'm glad you ate it.
I'd like to open it.
A big one.
Oh, that?
What did you say, Woo-chan?
Woo, it's big when it's whole, isn't it?
I'll take this paw-paw part.
Yeah, yeah.
Sit!
Oh, good!
Here's the paw madeleine!
Oh, he ate it!
Is it good?
Want some more?
Can it wait?
But I think I can.
Great!
Okay, Buchan.
Sit!
Great!
Wait! Wait!
Paw! Paw!
PIERPONT!
Whoo! Whoo!
Shimi-chan, hands on the ground!
Hey, boy, make a move!
Oh, wait, wait!
Woo-chan!
Woo-chan, your hand!
Look at me!
You're so cute.
I'm glad you're eating.
I'm going to spoil him.
Then I picked out a toy for Uichan.
I wonder if Ui-chan likes it.
Boom!
Look!
Ah!
Aah!
How do you like it?
Got it!
Woo-chan!
Woo-chan, give it to me!
Thank you, Woo-chan!
That's great! Now I want to play with it!
Oh! He'll play with it!
How should I play with this?
When Mi-chan says she can cache it, she waits a moment and then says...
What?
That's great!
I'm going in.
Ready, go!
Oh, my gosh!
You're so good!
You're good!
Thank you!
Let's throw this one, too.
Let's try this one, too.
Let's see if this one works too.
Here we go.
Ready?
Pow!
Oh, you're good!
You're good!
That's great!
I want everyone to see how cute I am with this mouthful.
C'mon, Pon!
Oh, medical condition.
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
Oh, it's so cute! It's so cute!
Sein Pon!
Oh, you're so good!
So cute!
I'm glad we had a lot of fun.
So, I feel like I've gotten to know Woo-chan pretty well.
I'm going to go to the pet store to buy some clothes for him!
Let's still have fun, Woo-chan!
Woo-chan!
Thank you very much.
So, I came to buy clothes for Ushimi-chan.
Please enjoy the photos and my narration of the shopping from here.
Yes, this is a close-up shot of Ui-chan, who is already too cute.
She is really cute. I've said "cute" about 10,000 times today.
Yes, and actually, the place where Uichan is standing is a fitting style.
In the fitting area, Uichan was fitted with the perfect cute outfit, and we were able to get it, so I would like to show it off to you all now.
Okay, next, I got some clothes that I think will suit Uichan, so I will have her put them on.
There are a lot of birds singing there.
Okay, I'll go.
Ta-da!
Look at Uichan!
If you see it in summer...
So cute! It's a pineapple, perfect for summer.
Will you come with me?
Thank you.
Too cute.
Then I'll do my best to get them to come. Like this.
I will.
Thank you.
It's a little bit difficult to get a good handle on it.
I don't know if I can do it.
May I ask you to lift your right leg?
Thank you for the big bend.
Thank you for the left leg.
Au-chan's out.
It's done.
So cute.
What? A baby?
There's a camera over there.
Let's go to the store, Woo.
Let's go to the store.
Woo-chan snapped!
He's so cute!
Too cute!
This outfit is pineapple, perfect for summer, and it's also insect repellent, and if you get it wet, it'll keep the bugs away.
It's so cute!
It's made of a material that's cool when wet, so I'm sure U-chan will be able to withstand the hot, hot weather from now on.
I'm sure he'll be able to withstand the hot, hot weather.
It's so cute!
I think so.
What should I do? He's really too cute.
I'm so sorry.
It's Riko.
I'm going to fall. I'm going to fall.
Auntie!
Yes, Auntie.
I don't like it here.
I don't like it.
Why are you such a good boy?
I don't like it here.
So, this time we have Ishimi and Moeko.
How did you all like it?
I've been so healed by Woo-chan's cuteness
I want to hug her right now!
Thank you, Woo-chan!
You made me feel better.
Thank you so much!
That's all I have to say.
If you want to see the show again, you may be able to meet Woo-chan, so please feel free to leave a comment and let us know what you think.
Please let us know if there are any places you think would be good to visit with your dog.
Thank you very much!
Thank you, Woo-chan!
Thank you very much.
See you soon!